{
  "units": {
    "Unit 1": [
      {
        "ID": 1,
        "QuestionText": "Pes",
        "Answer": "Dog"
      },
      {
        "ID": 2,
        "QuestionText": "Kočka",
        "Answer": "Cat"
      },
      {
        "ID": 3,
        "QuestionText": "Kůň",
        "Answer": "Horse"
      },
      {
        "ID": 4,
        "QuestionText": "Králík",
        "Answer": "Rabbit"
      },
      {
        "ID": 5,
        "QuestionText": "Pták",
        "Answer": "Bird"
      },
      {
        "ID": 6,
        "QuestionText": "Krab",
        "Answer": "Crab"
      },
      {
        "ID": 7,
        "QuestionText": "Pes",
        "Answer": "Dog"
      },
      {
        "ID": 8,
        "QuestionText": "Koala",
        "Answer": "Koala"
      },
      {
        "ID": 9,
        "QuestionText": "Lev",
        "Answer": "Lion"
      },
      {
        "ID": 10,
        "QuestionText": "Slon",
        "Answer": "Elephant"
      }
    ],
    "Unit 2": [
      {
        "ID": 11,
        "QuestionText": "Jablko",
        "Answer": "Apple"
      },
      {
        "ID": 12,
        "QuestionText": "Hruška",
        "Answer": "Pear"
      },
      {
        "ID": 13,
        "QuestionText": "Banán",
        "Answer": "Banana"
      },
      {
        "ID": 14,
        "QuestionText": "Mrkev",
        "Answer": "Carrot"
      },
      {
        "ID": 15,
        "QuestionText": "Rajče",
        "Answer": "Tomato"
      },
      {
        "ID": 16,
        "QuestionText": "Cibule",
        "Answer": "Onion"
      },
      {
        "ID": 17,
        "QuestionText": "Okurka",
        "Answer": "Cucumber"
      },
      {
        "ID": 18,
        "QuestionText": "Celer",
        "Answer": "Celery"
      },
      {
        "ID": 19,
        "QuestionText": "Brambory",
        "Answer": "Potatoes"
      },
      {
        "ID": 20,
        "QuestionText": "Kapusta",
        "Answer": "Cabbage"
      }
    ],
    "Unit 3": [
      {
        "ID": 21,
        "QuestionText": "Červená",
        "Answer": "Red"
      },
      {
        "ID": 22,
        "QuestionText": "Modrá",
        "Answer": "Blue"
      },
      {
        "ID": 23,
        "QuestionText": "Zelená",
        "Answer": "Green"
      },
      {
        "ID": 24,
        "QuestionText": "Žlutá",
        "Answer": "Yellow"
      },
      {
        "ID": 25,
        "QuestionText": "Oranžová",
        "Answer": "Orange"
      },
      {
        "ID": 26,
        "QuestionText": "Bílá",
        "Answer": "White"
      },
      {
        "ID": 27,
        "QuestionText": "Černá",
        "Answer": "Black"
      },
      {
        "ID": 28,
        "QuestionText": "Hnědá",
        "Answer": "Brown"
      },
      {
        "ID": 29,
        "QuestionText": "Šedá",
        "Answer": "Gray"
      },
      {
        "ID": 30,
        "QuestionText": "Růžová",
        "Answer": "Pink"
      }
    ],
    "Unit 4": [
      {
        "ID": 31,
        "QuestionText": "Slunce",
        "Answer": "Sun"
      },
      {
        "ID": 32,
        "QuestionText": "Déšť",
        "Answer": "Rain"
      },
      {
        "ID": 33,
        "QuestionText": "Sníh",
        "Answer": "Snow"
      },
      {
        "ID": 34,
        "QuestionText": "Vítr",
        "Answer": "Wind"
      },
      {
        "ID": 35,
        "QuestionText": "Oblaka",
        "Answer": "Clouds"
      },
      {
        "ID": 36,
        "QuestionText": "Bouřka",
        "Answer": "Thunderstorm"
      },
      {
        "ID": 37,
        "QuestionText": "Mlha",
        "Answer": "Fog"
      },
      {
        "ID": 38,
        "QuestionText": "Teplo",
        "Answer": "Heat"
      },
      {
        "ID": 39,
        "QuestionText": "Chladno",
        "Answer": "Cold"
      },
      {
        "ID": 40,
        "QuestionText": "Počasí",
        "Answer": "Weather"
      }
    ],
    "Unit 5": [
      {
        "ID": 41,
        "QuestionText": "Leden",
        "Answer": "January"
      },
      {
        "ID": 42,
        "QuestionText": "Únor",
        "Answer": "February"
      },
      {
        "ID": 43,
        "QuestionText": "Březen",
        "Answer": "March"
      },
      {
        "ID": 44,
        "QuestionText": "Duben",
        "Answer": "April"
      },
      {
        "ID": 45,
        "QuestionText": "Květen",
        "Answer": "May"
      },
      {
        "ID": 46,
        "QuestionText": "Červen",
        "Answer": "June"
      },
      {
        "ID": 47,
        "QuestionText": "Červenec",
        "Answer": "July"
      },
      {
        "ID": 48,
        "QuestionText": "Srpen",
        "Answer": "August"
      },
      {
        "ID": 49,
        "QuestionText": "Září",
        "Answer": "September"
      },
      {
        "ID": 50,
        "QuestionText": "Říjen",
        "Answer": "October"
      }
    ]
  }
}
